Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
"The Secret of Girls" (Episode 14)
سر البنات (الحلقة ١٤)
Come on.
تعال.
Let's grab a drink.
دعونا نتناول مشروبًا.
Let's celebrate that Xu Jingxi's back.
دعونا نحتفل بعودة Xu Jingxi.
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Don't drink too much.
لا تشرب كثيرا.
Jingxi.
جينغشي.
To tell the truth I've thought that you would come back.
لأكون صادقًا، لقد اعتقدت أنك ستعود.
But I didn't expect that you came back so soon.
ولكنني لم أتوقع عودتك بهذه السرعة.
Why, am I not welcome?
لماذا لا أرحب بي؟
How could you think that?
كيف يمكنك أن تفكر بذلك؟
I'm very happy for your back.
أنا سعيد جدًا بظهرك.
You're happy that you have someone working for you.
أنت سعيد لأن هناك شخص يعمل لديك.
I'm not that snobbish.
أنا لست متكبرًا إلى هذه الدرجة.
As for me
أما بالنسبة لي
I'm happy when I'm happy.
أنا سعيد عندما أكون سعيدًا.
Unlike some people who say one thing and mean another.
على عكس بعض الناس الذين يقولون شيئًا ويقصدون شيئًا آخر.
In their hearts they're very happy.
إنهم سعداء جدًا في قلوبهم.
But they're still so cold on the surface.
لكنهم ما زالوا باردين جدًا على السطح.
Who?
من؟
Who says one thing and means another?
من يقول شيئا ويقصد شيئا آخر؟
You.
أنت.
What did I do?
ماذا فعلت؟
You're good.
أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب.
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
Ignore her.
تجاهلها.
She's all mixed up.
إنها مختلطة كلها.
But having said that.
ولكن بعد أن قلت ذلك.
Have you done what you needed to do?
هل فعلت ما كان عليك فعله؟
Pretty much.
تقريباً.
But Sister Yun
لكن الأخت يون
I probably won't have time to work in the Inn this time.
ربما لن يكون لدي وقت للعمل في النزل هذه المرة.
Why?
لماذا؟
You need to leave?
هل تحتاج إلى المغادرة؟
I came here for travel last time.
لقد جئت إلى هنا للسفر في المرة الأخيرة.
But something unexpected happened
ولكن حدث شيء غير متوقع
and I lost all my things.
وفقدت كل أغراضي.
I didn't finish traveling.
لم أكمل السفر.
So...
لذا...
this time, I've decided that
هذه المرة قررت أن
I'll take a good look around.
سألقي نظرة جيدة حول المكان.
I heard that the sunrise here is very beautiful.
سمعت أن شروق الشمس هنا جميل جدًا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
You should spend a good time here.
ينبغي عليك قضاء وقت ممتع هنا.
The natural scenery is so great here.
المناظر الطبيعية هنا رائعة للغاية.
And there's that market.
وهناك هذا السوق.
It's very beautiful.
إنه جميل جداً.
Many young people go there.
يذهب العديد من الشباب إلى هناك.
Wen Shan.
ون شان.
Take her to play for few days
خذها للعب لبضعة أيام
I give you two days off.
سأعطيك يومين إجازة.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
You can use my car.
يمكنك استخدام سيارتي.
Go play around more.
اذهب للعب أكثر.
Okay.
تمام.
Thank you, Qiu Bei.
شكرا لك، تشيو باي.
Why are you only thanking Qiu Bei?
لماذا تشكر تشيو باي فقط؟
I bought her the car.
لقد اشتريت لها السيارة.
Okay.
تمام.
The most important is saying thank you to Sister Yun.
الأهم هو قول شكرًا للأخت يون.
But Sister Yun, please drink less.
لكن الأخت يون، من فضلك اشربي كمية أقل.
You drink so quickly.
تشرب بسرعة كبيرة.
Don't get too drunk.
لا تسكر كثيرا.
Her tolerance to alcohol is wild.
قدرتها على تحمل الكحول هائلة.
I've never seen her drunk.
لم أرها في حالة سكر أبدًا.
Really?
حقًا؟
Why do I feel that you always want to get me drunk?
لماذا أشعر أنك تريد أن تجعلني أسكر دائمًا؟
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
Does it benefit you if I get drunk?
هل ينفعك إذا سكرت؟
No
لا
I just haven't seen it
انا لم ارى ذلك
I'm curious.
أنا فضولي.
But to be honest Sister Yun really hasn't drank much.
ولكن لكي أكون صادقة، الأخت يون لم تشرب كثيرًا.
Is her tolerance really that good?
هل تسامحها جيد حقا؟
No
لا
I am so jealous.
أنا غيور جداً.
You should be envious.
ينبغي عليك أن تحسد.
Wen Shan.
ون شان.
When Xu Jingxi was drunk last time,
عندما كان Xu Jingxi في حالة سكر في المرة الأخيرة،
did she hug your neck and cry and make a scene?
هل عانقت رقبتك وبكت وأحدثت مشهدًا؟
How can you remember that so clearly?
كيف يمكنك أن تتذكر ذلك بوضوح؟
Who got drunk and hugged you while making a scene...
من الذي ثمل واحتضنك أثناء صنع مشهد ...
Talk about it!
تحدث عن ذلك!
Lame.
عاجِز.
Come on.
تعال.
Have a drink.
تناول مشروب.
Stop making a scene.
توقف عن إثارة المشهد.
Quickly
بسرعة
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
سأذهب إلى الحمام.
Are you trying to avoid drinking?
هل تحاول تجنب الشرب؟
No
لا
I'll come back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
Look, you've been called shy.
انظر، لقد تم تسميتك بالخجول.
It's all your fault.
إنه خطؤك كله.
When did you come back?
متى عدت؟
Just now.
الآن.
Are you feeling sick?
هل تشعر بالمرض؟
I'm fine
أنا بخير
I just... woke up so early in the morning.
لقد... استيقظت في الصباح الباكر.
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
Everything is OK.
كل شئ على ما يرام.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Lay down.
ارقد.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
We're almost done eating.
لقد انتهينا تقريبا من الأكل.
I'll clean up.
سأقوم بالتنظيف.
Lay down there.
استلقي هناك.
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
It's okay.
لا بأس.
It's not very good.
إنه ليس جيدا جدا.
Let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
You go to have a rest.
تذهب لتستريح.
Why are you so mean?
لماذا أنت حقير هكذا؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Have a good rest.
خذ قسطا جيدا من الراحة.
Are you fall asleep?
هل انت نائم؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You've found a job, right?
لقد وجدت وظيفة، أليس كذلك؟
Emmm...
اممم...
I don't want it.
انا لا اريد ذلك
Why?
لماذا؟
Have a guess.
خمن.
No, I don't.
لا أنا لا.
It's boring.
إنه ممل.
Because of me?
بسببي؟
I'm afraid of that someone can't sleep well
أخشى أن لا يتمكن أحد من النوم جيدًا
because of my absence.
بسبب غيابي.
And then they go to work with dark circles under their eyes the next day,
ثم يذهبون إلى العمل في اليوم التالي مع الهالات السوداء تحت أعينهم،
and scare away the customers.
وتخويف الزبائن.
Who? I don't know.
من؟ لا أعلم.
Right.
يمين.
Who could it be?
من يمكن أن يكون؟
I don't know, either.
أنا أيضا لا أعلم.
Mine is an ailment of the soul.
إن مرضي هو مرض الروح.
It can't be changed overnight
لا يمكن تغييره بين عشية وضحاها
I've tried my best.
لقد حاولت أن أبذل قصارى جهدي.
You're great.
أنت عظيم.
How long can you stay with me?
كم من الوقت يمكنك البقاء معي؟
For a lifetime?
مدى الحياة؟
Wen Shan.
ون شان.
I don't know how long that I can stay with you.
لا أعلم كم من الوقت يمكنني البقاء معك.
But...
لكن...
If I can be next to you,
إذا كان بإمكاني أن أكون بجانبك،
you could sleep well,
يمكنك النوم جيدا،
and gradually move away from the darkness,
والابتعاد تدريجيا عن الظلام،
I hope I could be with you for a long time.
أتمنى أن أتمكن من البقاء معك لفترة طويلة.
Wen Shan.
ون شان.
I don't have anyone worth caring about.
ليس لدي أحد يستحق الاهتمام.
Of course, it seems that no one cares about me.
وبطبيعة الحال، يبدو أن لا أحد يهتم بي.
But...
لكن...
people go on living,
الناس يستمرون في العيش،
there must be something to care about.
لا بد أن يكون هناك ما يستحق الاهتمام.
Someone to care about.
شخص ما يهتم لأمره.
Only in times of pain and despair.
فقط في أوقات الألم واليأس.
Can people live a good life,
هل يستطيع الناس أن يعيشوا حياة جيدة؟
and try their best to live.
ويحاولون جاهدين أن يعيشوا.
Only in this way can life be valuable.
بهذه الطريقة فقط يمكن للحياة أن تكون ذات قيمة.
Even a little bit of it is good.
حتى القليل منه جيد.
Now.
الآن.
You are the one that I care about the most.
أنت الشخص الذي أهتم به أكثر من غيره.